nobacks.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy | noBACKS

We take your right to privacy seriously. This Policy discloses the privacy practices for this website (the “Site”). In reviewing this Policy, you can expect to be notified of: what personally identifiable information of yours is collected; the organization collecting the information; how the information is used; with whom the information may be shared.

our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address, when you visit the Site. Your IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data — such as the web pages you view. Your IP address does not identify you personally.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by advertising partners and ad networks. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information please contact us.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Inherent risks of the Internet**

All information gathered on the Site is encrypted for storage within site-controlled database. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Of course, any information you include in a message you post to any message board, forum or other public posting area is available to anyone with Internet access. If you do not want people to know your email address, for example, do not include it in any message you post publicly.

**A note regarding the privacy of children**

Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else.

**Changes to this Policy**

The Web is an evolving medium. If we need to change our privacy policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect. Of course, our use of information gathered while the current policy is in effect will always be consistent with the current policy, even if we change that policy later.
